<Document>
<<<<<<< HEAD
  # Cargo Bounties
  While [textlink="Cargo" link="Cargo"] can make [color=cyan]spesos[color] selling just about anything, more spesos can be made by fulfilling [color=cyan]bounties[/color] found through the Cargo Bounty Computer.

  ## Starting Bounties
=======
  # Запросы отдела снабжения
  [textlink="Отдел снабжения" link="Cargo"] всегда может заработать, продавая товары, когда им вздумается. Однако есть способы заработать ещё больше денег, если более избирательно подходить к тому, что и когда вы продаёте. Один из таких способов - [color=#a4885c]запросы[/color].
>>>>>>> 52c7c8a11c86fbafbf2cf46e548fe9f7f836ce66

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ComputerCargoBounty"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PaperCargoBountyManifest"/>
  </Box>
<<<<<<< HEAD

  To start a bounty, open the bounty screen by interacting with the [color=cyan]Cargo Bounty Computer[/color]. The Cargo Bounty Computer maintains a list of all the current bounties and lets you either print out a label or skip it.

  - Printing the label gives you a [color=cyan]Bounty Manifest[/color] listing the goods that need to be acquired. You can print out infinite Bounty Manifests, so ensure you are not repeating the same work as another Cargo Technician.

  - Skipping a bounty replaces that bounty with a new one, as there can only be six active bounties at any time. Skipping has a 15-minute cooldown and voids that bounty, which may anger other Cargo Technicians working on it.

  ## Fulfilling Bounties

=======
  На каждой станции есть определённое количество доступных запросов. Их можно проверить на [color=#a4885c]консоли запросов[/color], которая показывает следующую информацию о них:
  - Какие предметы нужны для выполнения запроса
  - Сколько денег вы получите за выполнение запроса
  - Сколько времени осталось до истечения срока запроса

  При условии, что вы сможете достать все предметы для этого, затратив минимум времени и средств, вы сможете завершить запрос и получить значительно большую сумму, чем если бы вы продавали предметы обычным способом.

  ## Выполнение запросов
>>>>>>> 52c7c8a11c86fbafbf2cf46e548fe9f7f836ce66
  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PaperCargoBountyManifest"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CrateGenericSteel"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="AppraisalTool"/>
  </Box>
<<<<<<< HEAD

  With the [color=cyan]Bounty Manifest[/color], it is now up to you to collect the required goods. Most departments will give you what you need by asking for it with a Bounty Manifest.

  Once you have collected the goods, return to the cargo bay and put the goods inside an empty [color=cyan]Crate[/color]. After everything is in the crate, close it, and then apply the Bounty Manifest to it.

  To verify the completion of a bounty, use the [color=cyan]Appraisal Tool[/color] on it. It should say that it confirms that the bounty has been completed.

  ## Selling Bounties

  <Box>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="PaperCargoBountyManifest"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CrateGenericSteel"/>
    <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="CargoPalletSell"/>
  </Box>

  Once you have verified that you have completed the bounty, follow the same steps as selling anything else.

  Just transport it to the [color=cyan]Trading Station[/color], sell it, and you are done!

  When you return, there should be a new bounty to take its place.
=======
  Как только вы соберёте предметы, необходимые для запроса, завершить его будет проще простого.:
  - Поместите все предметы в ящик и [bold]закройте его![/bold].
  - Возьмите этикетку манифеста, нажав кнопку [color=#a4885c]распечатать этикетку[/color] на консоли запросов.
  - Поместите этикетку на ящик, в котором находятся предметы.
  - Переместите ящик на грузовой шаттл.
  - Продайте его.

  Вот и всё! После того как вы выполните эти действия, запрос должен исчезнуть с компьютера, а на его месте появится новый.
>>>>>>> 52c7c8a11c86fbafbf2cf46e548fe9f7f836ce66
</Document>
